Guide to the Arthur Levitt, Jr. Papers
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series XIII: SEC Correspondents Index
  - Fierle, Robert J. American Precision Industries, FROM: Aug. 2, 1993; TO: Aug. 12, 1993
  - Figel, Reid M. US Attorney, FROM: Feb. 15, 1997
  - Figlewski, Stephen New York University Leonard N. Stern School of Business, TO: May 2, 1995
  - Figueres, Muni Costa Rica, FROM: Mar. 27, 1998; May 27, 1998; TO: Jun. 4, 1998
  - Figueres Olsen, Jose Maria President, Costa Rica, FROM: Jul. 18, 1997; TO: Aug. 8, 1997
  - Fineron, J. FROM: Dec. 15, 1999; TO: Mar. 14, 2000
  - Fink, Matthew P. Investment Company Institute, FROM: Feb. 7, 1995; Apr. 5, 1995; Apr. 17, 1995; May 19, 1995; May 23, 1995; Sep. 28, 1995; May 20, 1996; May 23, 1996; Nov. 11, 1996; Nov. 13, 1997; Jul. 9, 1998; Sep. 9, 1999; Sep. 15, 1999; Oct. 13, 1999; Dec. 22, 1999; TO: Jan. 18, 1995; Feb. 24, 19
  - Finn, David Ruder-Finn, Inc. FROM: Jan. 8, 199[7]; TO: Jan. 30, 1995; Feb. 7, 1997
  - Fishburn, Dudley Economist, FROM: Nov. 17, 1994; Nov. 13, 1995; May 22, 1996; TO: Jun. 21, 1996
  - Fisher, George M.C. Eastman Kodak Co. TO: May 1, 1995
  - Fisher, Pamela S. Boy Scouts of America, FROM: Mar. 14, 1998 (filed under Mar. 24, 1998)
  - Fisher, Peggy US SEC - Division of Corporation Finance, TO: Oct. 23, 1995
  - Fisher, Richard B. Morgan Stanley & Co., Inc. TO: Feb. 17, 1995; Mar 2, 1995; Mar. 27, 1995; Apr. 20, 1995; Jun. 7, 1995; Jan. 30. 1997; Apr. 10, 1997
  - Fitterman, Mark D. US SEC - Division of Market Regulation, TO: Feb. 17 1995
  - Fitzgerald, Jim, TO: Apr. 20, 1995
  - Fitzgerald, Kathleen New York Stock Exchange, TO: Feb. 17 1995
  - [Fleesclund], Ed. FROM: Dec. 16, 1994; TO: Jan. 17, 1995; [Feb. 17 1995]
  - Fitzgerald, Peter US Senate, FROM: Feb. 23, 2000 (Sturm, Robert); TO: May 3, 2000
  - Flaherty, Robert J. Equities Magazine, FROM: Dec. 23, 1997; Feb. 3, 2000; TO: Jan. 5, 1998; Feb. 9, 2000
  - Flanagan, Kathleen M. John Nuveen & Co., Inc. TO: Sep. 13, 1995
  - Flanigan, Thomas E. FROM: Jun. 7, 1997; TO: Aug. 1, 1997
  - Fleischer, Arthur, Jr. Fried, Frank, Harris, Shriver & Jacobson, TO: Mar. 5, 1998; Jan. 29, 2001
  - Fleischer, Spencer Morgan Stanley International, TO: Mar. 7, 1995
  - Fleischman, Edward H. Linklaters, FROM: Sep. 8, 1999; TO: Oct. 30, 1998; Sep. 22, 1999
  - Flom, Joseph H. Skadden, Arps, Slate, Meagher & Flom, TO: Mar. 5, 1998
  - Flomenhaft, Joelyn, TO: Apr. 20, 1995
  - Flores, Julian M. Security Traders Association of Washington, DC, TO: May 14, 1998
  - Flynn, Darcy US SEC - Division of Enforcement, TO: Jun. 18, 1998
  - Fob, James Governor, AL, TO: Oct. 23, 1995 (+list)
  - Fogarty, John F. FROM: Mar. 10, 1994
  - Foley, Gerard National Association of Securities Dealers, TO: Feb. 17 1995
  - Folger, Bitsey City Lights School, FROM: Feb. 29, 1996; TO: Mar. 13, 1996
  - Fong, Matt Treasurer, CA, FROM: Nov. 3, 1995; Sep. 10, 1996; TO: Feb. 9, 1996; Sep. 27, 1996
  - Fons, Randall US SEC - Southeast Regional Office, TO: Apr. 15, 1999
  - Foran, Margaret M. ITT Corporation, TO: Dec. 23, 1996
  - Forbes, Malcolm S., Jr. Forbes Magazine, FROM: May 10, 1995; TO: May 17, 1995
  - Forney, Robert H. Chicago Stock Exchange, FROM: Dec. 20, 1995; Jan. 12, 1996; Apr. 16, 1997; Jun. 29, 1998 (filed under Jackson, Jesse, Sr., Jul. 9, 1998); Jun. 16, 1999; Oct. 4, 1999; Jan. 6, 2000; TO: Sep. 13, 1995; Oct. 25, 1995; Jan. 29, 1996; Jan. 30, 1996; Mar. 7, 1997; May 8, 1997; Jul. 1
  - Fosella, Vito J. US House of Representatives, FROM: Sep. 27, 1999; TO: Oct. 12, 1999
  - Foss, Jay, TO: Apr. 20, 1995
  - Foss, Lawrence Chase Securities, Inc. TO: Apr. 8, 1998
  - Fosssella, Vito J. US House of Representatives, FROM: Jan. 10, 1999; TO: Feb. 7, 2000
  - Foster, Bob US House of Representatives - Office of Rep. Oxley, TO: Mar. 5, 1997
  - Foster, John M. (Neel) Financial Accounting Standards Board, FROM: Apr. 25, 1996; Apr. 13, 1998; Jun. 16, 1998; TO: Apr. 21, 1998; Apr. 30, 1998; Jul. 10, 1998
  - Fox, David W. Chicago Stock Exchange, TO: Mar. 7, 1997; Feb. 22, 1999
  - Fox, Jean Ann Consumer Federation of America, FROM: May 9, 2000; TO: Jun. 20, 2000
  - Fox, Lawrence J. American Bar Association, FROM: Dec. 1, 1995; TO: Jan. 2, 1996
  - Fraiman, Robert J. FROM: Jul. 30, 1993; TO: Aug. 9, 1993
  - Franchella, Richard Paine Webber, Inc. TO: Feb. 17 1995
  - Frank, Barney US House of Representatives, FROM: Apr. 27, 1995; Oct. 10, 1996; Aug. 26, 1997; Oct. 28, 1997; Nov. 18, 1997; May 9, 2000; Jul. 10, 2000; TO: May 12, 1995; Dec. 10, 1996; Oct. 6, 1997; Nov. 25, 1997; Jun. 20, 2000; Aug. 29, 2000
  - Franke, Richard J. John Nuveen & Co., Inc. TO: Sep. 13, 1995
  - Frazier, Fran American Business Conference, TO: Oct. 2, 1998
  - Frederick, Paul A. Frederick & Company, Inc. FROM: Oct. 2, 1997; TO: Apr. 20, 1995; Nov. 17, 1997
  - Freeman, James S. Olde Discount Corporation, TO: Apr. 20, 1995
  - Freeman, Paul Charles Schwab & Co, Inc. TO: Feb. 17 1995
  - Freeman, Richard A. Wasserstein Perella & Co, Inc. FROM: Mar. 10, 1995; TO: Mar. 29, 1995
  - Frenkel, Ya'akov J. Bank of Israel, TO: Apr. 25, 1997
  - Freund, William C. Lubin Graduate School of Business, Pace University, FROM: Aug. 9, 1993; TO: Aug. 13, 1993
  - Fribourg, Paul J. ContiGroup Companies, Inc. TO: Oct. 12, 1999
  - Friedland, Stuart, FROM: Aug. 2, 1993; May 26, 1998; TO: Aug. 9, 1993; Jun. 3, 1998
  - Friedman, Felice US SEC, TO: Jun. 24, 1999
  - Friedman, Stephen Goldman Sachs & Co. FROM: Aug. 9, 1993; TO: Aug. 24, 1993
  - Friedman, Stephen J. Association of the Bar of the City of New York - Committee on Securities Regulation, from: Nov. 15, 1995 (Clinton); to: Nov. 30, 1995
  - Friedman, Stephen J. Equitable Life Assurance Society, FROM: Aug. 5, 1993;TO: Aug. 24, 1993
  - Friedman, Stephen J. Equitable Life Assurance Society; Debevoise & Plimpton, FROM: Nov. 8, 1995; TO: Nov. 27, 1995; Aug. 29, 1997
  - Frist, Bill US Senate, TO: Jan. 30, 1995; Aug. 21 1995; Jan. 23, 1998
  - Friedman, Thomas New York Times, TO: Nov. 7, 2000
  - Frisa, Dan US House of Representatives, FROM: Aug. 9, 1995; TO: Sep. 12, 1995
  - Fronsdal, Kjell Oslo Bors, Norway, TO: Apr. 10, 1997
  - Frost, Martin US House of Representatives, TO: Mar. 27, 1995
  - Frost, Timothy T. Pioneer First Voucher, Russia, FROM: Aug. 26, 1996; TO: Sep. 13, 1996
  - Frucher, Meyer S. Philadelphia Stock Exchange, FROM: Jun. 2, 1999; TO: Feb. 22, 1999; Jun. 15, 1999; Oct. 1, 1999
  - Fujioka, Margaret J. National Asian Pacific Bar Association, FROM: Feb. 9, 1998; TO: Mar. 25, 1998
  - Fuld, Richard S., Jr. Lehman Brothers, Inc. FROM: Nov. 30, 1996; TO: Feb. 17, 1995; Mar 2, 1995; Mar. 27, 1995; Apr. 20, 1995; Jun. 7, 1995; Jan. 29, 1996; Apr. 10, 1997; Oct. 17, 1997; Apr. 8, 1998; Jul. 21, 1998; Oct. 22, 1998; Nov. 23, 1998; Dec. 28, 1998; Jan. 5, 1999; Jan. 29, 2001
  - Fuller, H. Lawrence Amoco, TO: May 1, 1995
  - Fulton, Kathryn US SEC - Director of Legislative Affairs, FROM: Jan. 30, 1995 (Rep. Wolf); Mar. 3, 1995 (Sayer); TO: Jan. 9, 1995 (Rep. Wolf)
  - Furer, Lewis, TO: Apr. 20, 1995
  - Furlong, Mary Anne New York Stock Exchange, TO: Feb. 17 1995
  - Furman, Gregory J. Bergdorf Goodman, FROM: Jul. 27, 1993; TO: Aug. 4, 1993
  - Furman, Roy L. Furman Selz, Inc. FROM: Jul. 27, 1993; TO: Aug. 9, 1993
  - Furse, Elizabeth US House of Representatives, TO: Feb. 18, 1997; Mar. 5, 1997
  - Fushiya, Kazuhiko Ministry of Finance Securities Bureau, Japan, FROM: Jun. 24, 1998; TO: Jun. 29, 1998
  - Futter, Ellen American Museum of Natural History, TO: Jan. 29, 2001
  - Gabr, Shafik American Chamber of Commerce in Egypt, FROM: Feb. 29, 1995; Apr. 21, 1997; TO: Mar. 11, 1996; May 2, 1997
  - Gallo, Lynda, TO: Apr. 20, 1995
  - Gamboa, John C. Greenlining Institute, FROM: Oct. 7, 1998(+others); TO: Oct. 15, 1998
  - Gannon, John US SEC - Office of Investor Education, FROM: Dec. 4, 1998; TO: Oct. 9, 1998 (RE: Salas, Selma)
  - Ganske, Greg US House of Representatives, FROM: Jul. 14, 1998; TO: Feb. 18, 1997; Mar. 5, 1997; Aug. 18, 1998; Apr. 12, 2000; Jul. 13, 2000
  - Gard, Steven J. Page & Bacek, TO: Apr. 20, 1995
  - Gardinger, Robert M. Morgan Stanley Dean Witter, FROM: Jul. 27, 2000; TO: Aug. 15, 2000
  - Gardner, Tom Motley Fool, Inc. TO: Nov. 27, 2000
  - Garten, Jeffrey E. Yale School of Management, FROM: May 2, 1997; Sep. 23, 1997; TO: May 20, 1997; Jan. 29, 2001
  - Gatzek, Deborah R. Franklin Resources, Inc. TO: Mar. 16, 1999
  - Gaul, Hans Michael VEBA Aktiengesellschaft, Germany, FROM: Oct. 14, 1997; TO: Dec. 2, 1997
  - Gault, Ronald T. J.P. Morgan Securities, Inc. FROM: Aug. 26, 1993: TO: Sep. 13, 1993
  - Gavin, Paula L. YMCA of Greater NY, FROM: Jan. 22, 1996; TO: Feb. 20, 1996
  - Gaynor, Thomas J. Department of Law and Public Safety, NJ, TO: Apr. 21, 1995
  - Geist, Andrew J. US SEC - Northeast Regional Office, TO: Feb. 24, 1995
  - Gejdenson, Sam US House of Representatives, FROM: May 14, 1997
  - Gelfond, Larry Gelfond Hochstadt Pangburn, TO: Nov. 27, 2000
  - Gensler, Gary US Department of Treasury, FROM: Nov. 1, 1999; TO: Nov. 8, 1999
  - George, James Covert Intelligence Associates, Inc. TO: Apr. 20, 1995
  - George, Sylvia Covert Intelligence Associates, Inc. TO: Apr. 20, 1995
  - George, Raymond E., Jr. FROM: Dec. 16, 1999; TO: Jan. 19, 2000
  - George, William Covert Intelligence Associates, Inc. TO: Apr. 20, 1995
  - George, William W. Medtronic, Inc. FROM: Oct. 17, 2000; TO: Feb. 19, 1999; Oct. 27, 2000
  - Georges, John A. International Paper, FROM: Nov. 30, 1995; TO: Dec. 7, 1995
  - Gerber, A. Richard Securities Commission, PA, FROM: Jun. 17, 1996; Mar. 3, 1996; TO: Jul. 11, 1996; Apr. 16, 1998
  - Gerrish, Donald H. Town Manager, Brunswick, ME; International City/County Management Association; FROM: Mar. 18, 1997; TO: Mar. 26, 1997
  - Gersh, Bernard Georgetown University Medical Center, TO: Jun. 23 1995 (re: Kimberly Solomon)
  - Gervin, Arthur Respect for Law Alliance, Inc. FROM: Sep. 21, 1995; Oct. 17, 1995; Jul. 17, 1997; TO: Sep. 26, 1995; Oct. 25, 1995; Jul. 23, 1997
  - Gettinger, Jason R. US SEC - Northeast Regional Office, TO: Feb. 24, 1995
  - Gevirtz, Don L. Foothill Group, Inc. FROM: Aug. 21, 1995 (A. Levitt III); TO: Aug. [29]; 1995
  - Geyer, Thomas E. Department of Commerce, OH, FROM: Nov. 27, 1997; Apr. 13, 1998; TO: Jan. 17, 1997; Apr. 21, 1998
  - Giamanco, Joseph GHM, Inc. TO: Feb. 20, 1996
  - Giles, Bob Media Studies Center, TO: Sep. 14, 1998
  - Gillan, Kayla J. Public Employees Retirement System, CA, TO: Nov. 27, 2000
  - Gillmor, Paul E. US House of Representatives, FROM: May 23, 1997 (filed under Buffet, Warren, Aug. 25, 1997); TO: Feb. 18, 1997; Mar. 5, 1997; Mar. 13, 1997
  - Gillogly, Donald DLS Group, Inc. TO: Feb. 17, 1995
  - Gilman, Benjamin A. US House of Representatives, FROM: Nov. 24, 1997; TO: Dec. 17, 1997
  - Gilson, Ronald J. Stanford University Law School, TO: Mar. 16, 1999
  - Gingrich, Newt US House of Representatives, TO: Jan. 6, 1995; Jun. 16. 1995; Dec. 29, 1995; Mar. 4, 1996; Jun. 4, 1996; Jun. 19, 1996; Sep. 11, 1996; Sep. 25, 1997; May 4, 1998; Sep. 30, 1998
  - Ginsburg, David, TO: Sep. 16, 1998 (RE: Douglas, William)
  - Ginsburg, Mark New York University Leonard N. Stern School of Business, TO: Oct. 10, 1995
  - Ginsburg, Ruth Bader US Supreme Court, TO: Oct. 5, 1998
  - Giordano, Nicholas A. Philadelphia Stock Exchange, FROM: Aug. 9, 1993; Feb. 8, 1995 (IPO Study); Feb. 10, 1995; Jan. 12, 1996; Feb. 5, 1997; TO: Aug. 13, 1993; Jan. 12, 1995; Feb. 17, 1995; Feb. 17, 1995 (IPO Study); Mar. 8, 1995; Oct. 25, 1995; Dec. 7, 1995; Jan. 30, 1996; Feb. 14, 1997; Mar. 7, 1997
  - Gitenstein, Mark H. Mayer, Brown & Platt, TO: Apr. 23, 1997
  - Givens, Beth Privacy Rights Clearinghouse, FROM: May 9, 2000; TO: Jun. 20, 2000
  - Glaser, Rob RealNetworks, Inc. TO: Jun. 13, 2000
  - Glasser, Eugene J. Sweig/Glasser Advisers, TO: Apr. 20, 1995
  - Glasser, Lynn S. Simon & Schuster Professional Information Group, FROM: Aug. 9, 1993; Apr. 25, 1995; TO: Aug. 12, 1993; May 3, 1995
  - Glasser, Stephen A. Simon & Schuster Professional Information Group, FROM: Aug. 9, 1993; Apr. 25, 1995; TO: Aug. 12, 1993; May 3, 1995
  - Glassman, James K. American Enterprise Institute for Public Policy Research, FROM: Jul. 15, 1997 (McIntosh, David); TO: Jan. 29, 2001
  - Glassman, Zoe John F. Kennedy Center for the Performing Arts, FROM: Aug. 28, 1998; TO: Sep. 1, 1998
  - Glatstein, David Barre & Company, Inc. TO: Apr. 20, 1995
  - Glauber, Robert Harvard University - JFK School of Government; National Association of Security Dealers (NASD), TO: Dec. 1, 1998; Jan. 29, 2001
  - Glenn, John US Senate, FROM: Jul. 29, 1998; TO: Dec. 29, 1995; Nov. 20, 1997; Sep. 29, 1998
  - Glickman, Andrew Z. US SEC - Office of General Counsel, TO: Oct. 9, 1996
  - Godrish, Orit Bain & Co. TO: Jan. 29, 2001
  - Goettsch, Craig A. Insurance Division, IA (Supt. Of Securities), TO: Apr. 21, 1995
  - Goetzmann, Darlene Fidelity Investments, TO: Feb. 17 1995
  - Goizueta, Robert C. Coca-Cola Company, TO: May 1, 1995
  - Goldberg, Bruce TJFR Business News Reporter, TO: Feb. 8, 2000 (Business News Luminaries)
  - Goldfus, Donald W. Apogee Enterprises, Inc. FROM: Jan. 24, 1995; TO: Jan. 31, 1995
  - Goldmark, Peter C., Jr. Herald Tribune, FROM: Jul. 31, 1998
  - Goldschmidt, Harvey Columbia University Law School, TO: Oct. 23, 1995; Mar. 6, 1996; Nov. 6, 1996; Nov. 24, 1998
  - Goldsmith, Barry R. US SEC - Division of Enforcement, TO: Aug. 9, 1996; Jun. 4, 1998
  - Goldstein, Joseph Kirkpatrick & Lockhart LLP, TO: [Nov. 12], 1999
  - Goldstein, Louis L. Comptroller of Treasury, MD, FROM: Aug. 13, 1993: TO: Sep. 13, 1993
  - Goldstein, Michael Toys RUs, Inc. FROM: May 29, 1996; TO: Jun. 12, 1996
  - Golub, Harvey American Express Company, FROM: Aug. 25, 1995; Nov. 24, 1998; TO: Aug. 31, 1995; Dec. 7, 1998; Nov. 27, 2000
  - Gonzalez, Charles A. US House of Representatives, FROM: Jan. 20, 2000; May 9, 2000; TO: May 19, 2000; Jun. 20, 2000
  - Gonzalez, Henry US House of Representatives, TO: Mar. 27, 1995
  - Gonzalez-Taboada, Jose Universidad de Puerto Rico, FROM: Nov. 23, 1998; TO: Nov. 23, 1998 (Turner, Lynn)
  - Gonzon, Paul Kirkpatrick & Lockhart LLP, TO: Mar. 16, 1999
  - Goodhart, Cori J. American Association of Retired Persons, TO: Apr. 6, 1998
  - Gooding, Paul H. Mimlic Sales Corporation, TO: Apr. 20, 1995
  - Goodison, Sir Nicholas TSB Group plc, FROM: Oct. 14, 1993; TO: Oct. 29, 1993
  - Goodling, William F. US House of Representatives, TO: Apr. 7, 1997
  - Goodwin, Donald J. Smith Barney Shearson Inc. TO: Apr. 20, 1995
  - Goldin, Harrison Jay Goldin Associates, FROM: May 23, 1995; Nov. 6, 1996; Apr. 8, 1998; [n.d]; TO: Apr. 15, 1998
  - Goodwin, Doris K. TO: Jan. 6, 1998 (bio info)
  - Gordon, Bart US House of Representatives, FROM: Mar. 26, 1997; TO: Apr. 25, 1997
  - Gordon, Janet, TO: Apr. 20, 1995
  - Gordon, Robert N. Twenty-First Securities Corporation, TO: Apr. 20, 1995; Jul. 7, 1995
  - Gordon, Miles Z. Financial Network Investment Corporation; M.B. Vick & Co; TO: Mar 2, 1995; Apr. 20, 1995; Sep. 13, 1995
  - Gore, Albert D., Jr. Vice President, USA, FROM: Nov. 6, 1996; Jun. 23, 1997; TO: Jan. 6, 1995; Jun. 16. 1995; Jul. 19, 1995; Dec. 29, 1995; Jan. 26, 1996; Feb. 27, 1996; Mar. 4, 1996; Jun. 4, 1996; Jun. 19, 1996; Sep. 11, 1996; Dec. 5, 1996; Sep. 25, 1997; May 28, 1998; Sep. 30, 1998; Jun. 11, 1
  - Gorman, Lon Schwab Capital Markets & Trading, TO: Oct. 15, 1999
  - Goss, Robert P. Certified Financial Planner Board of Standards, FROM: Mar. 10, 1995; TO: Apr. 4, 1995
  - Gottesman, Alan J. FROM: May 11, 1995; TO: Jun. 20, 1995
  - Gottrell, Rick G. Financial Services Board, South Africa, TO: Jun. 25, 1999
  - Grabish, Richard F. Securities Industry Association, FROM: Jul. 23, 1993; TO: Aug. 4, 1993
  - Gramlich, Edward Federal Reserve Board, TO: Oct. 21, 1998
  - Gramm, Phil US Senate, FROM: Feb. 6, 1996; Apr. 25, 1997; Mar. 24, 1998; Dec. 17, 1999; Feb. 23, 2000; Nov. 15, 2000; TO: Mar. 27, 1995; Aug. 10, 1995; Sep. 5, 1995; Nov. 20, 1995; Dec. 29, 1995; Jan. 19, 1996; Feb. 23, 1996; Apr. 9, 1997; Apr. 11, 1997; May 5, 1997; Jul. 24
  - Grammatica, Joy US SEC - Production Support, TO: Sep. 29, 1995
  - Grams, Rod US Senate, FROM: Feb. 26, 1999; TO: Mar. 9, 1999; Oct. 26, 2000
  - Grano, Joseph Paine Webber, Inc. TO: Jul. 7, 1995
  - Grant, Elliott M. FROM: Jun. 13, 1995; TO: Jul. 19, 1995
  - Grant, Susan National Consumers League, FROM: May 9, 2000; TO: Jun. 20, 2000
  - Grasso, Richard A. New York Stock Exchange, FROM: Feb. 5, 1997; Oct. 12, 1998; TO: Jan. 12, 1995; Feb. 17, 1995; Apr. 26, 1995; Jul. 7, 1995; Jul. 31, 1995; Sep. 5, 1995; Jul. 24, 1996; Feb. 14, 1997; Aug. 8, 1997; Sep. 9, 1997; Oct. 23, 1997; Oct. 26, 1998; Feb. 22, 1999; Mar. 24, 1999; Jul. 26, 1
  - Grayson, Eugene Travellers Equities Sales, Inc. TO: Mar 2, 1995; Apr. 20, 1995
  - Gray, Elizabeth CNS, TO: Mar. 9, 2000
  - Grayson, E. C. Spencer Stuart, FROM: Dec. 11, 1995; TO: Jan. 22, 1996
  - Greber, Robert M. Pacific Stock Exchange, FROM: May 30, 1995; Feb. 5, 1997; TO: Jun. 22, 1995; Feb. 14, 1997; Mar. 7, 1997; Feb. 22, 1999
  - Green, Gene US House of Representatives, TO: Mar. 27, 1995
  - Green, Harry F., III Philadelphia Stock Exchange, FROM: Jun. 10, 1998; TO: Jun. 30, 1998
  - Green, Joseph DLS Group, Inc. TO: Feb. 17, 1995
  - Green, Mark US SEC - Division of Corporation Finance, FROM: Mar. 1, 2000; TO: Mar. 15, 2000
  - Green, Micah S. Public Securities Association; Bond Market Association, FROM: Aug. 23, 1993; Oct. 20, 1997; TO: Aug. 27, 1993; Jan. 4, 1995; Nov. 13, 1997
  - Green, Robert, FROM: Oct. 12, 1993; TO: Oct. 29, 1993
  - Green, Ronald M Dartmouth College, TO: Apr. 26, 1995
  - Greenberg, Alan C. Bear, Stearns & Co, Inc. TO: Feb. 17, 1995
  - Greenberg, Daniel Electro Rent Corp. FROM: Aug. 1, 1993; Sep. 3, 1996; TO: Aug. 9, 1993
  - Greenberg, Jack M. McDonald's Corp. FROM: Oct. 6, 1998;TO: Oct. 26, 1998
  - Greenberg, Martin H. Tekno-Books, FROM: Mar. 21, 1997
  - Greenberg, Maurice R. American International Group, Inc. FROM: Nov. 10, 1997; TO: Dec. 18, 1997
  - Greenberg, Sanford D. Chatfield Dean & Co. TO: Apr. 20, 1995
  - Greene, Ainsworth International Association for Financial Planning, TO: May 14, 1998
  - Greene, Milton A. Investment Management and Research, Inc. TO: Apr. 20, 1995
  - Greenhill, Robert F. Smith Barney Shearson Inc. TO: Feb. 17, 1995; Mar 2, 1995; Apr. 20, 1995; Jun. 7, 1995
  - [Greenspan] Treasury and Civil Service Committee, UK, FROM: Jan. 30, 1995 (See Arnold, Thomas of Apr. 18, 1995)
  - Greenles, Chris US SEC, TO: May 3, 1995
  - Greenspan, Alan Federal Reserve System - Board of Governors, FROM: May 26, 1995; Jun. 4, 1998 (filed under Oxley, Jun. 15, 1998); Oct. 14, 1999; TO: Jun. 21, 1995; Nov. 14, 1995; Dec. 5, 1997; May 21, 1998; Jun. 3, 1998; Mar. 9, 1999; Oct. 29, 1999
  - Greenwald, Gerald United Airlines, FROM: Jun. 3, 1996; TO: Mar. 19, 1996
  - Greenwood, James G. US House of Representatives, TO: Feb. 18, 1997
  - Gregg, Judd US Senate, TO: Jan. 19, 1996
  - Grey, Martin M. Smith Barney, Harris, Uphan & Co, Inc. FROM: Jul. 27, 1993; TO: Aug. 4, 1993
  - Griffin, Dustin H. FROM: Jul. 27, 1993; TO: Aug. 13, 1993
  - Gross, Bernard M. FROM: Mar. 1, 1994
  - Griffin, Mark J. Securities Division, UT (Director); North American Securities Administrators Association, Inc. FROM: Nov. 27, 1996; TO: Apr. 21, 1995; Jan. 27, 1997
  - Grimm, Daniel K. Treasurer, WA, FROM: Oct. 4, 1995; TO: Oct. 24, 1995
  - Gross, Bernard L. Charles River Investment Advisors, TO: Apr. 20, 1995
  - Gross, Holly A. Downtown Jaycees, DC, FROM: Apr. 4, 1995 (filed under Holland, Patricia, May 12, 1995)
  - Grove, Andrew S. Intel Corp. TO: May 1, 1995
  - Groves, Philip L. TO: Apr. 20, 1995
  - Groves, Ray J. Ernest & Young; Legg Mason Merchant Banking, Inc. FROM: Jul. 28, 1993; [May 11], 1995; Oct. 24, 2000; TO: Aug. 4, 1993; Jun. 7, 1995; Nov. 27, 2000
  - Gruber, Martin J. New York University Leonard N. Stern School of Business, TO: May 2, 1995
  - Grundfest, Joseph A. Stanford University Law School, FROM: Apr. 5, 1995; TO: May 2, 1995
  - Grundhofer, John F. First Bank System, Inc. FROM: Feb. 14, 1996; TO: May 1, 1995; Mar. 1, 1996
  - Gualtieri, John P. Prudential Insurance Company of America, TO: Feb. 17, 1995
  - Gu, Chen, FROM: Nov. 12, 1996; TO: Nov. 26, 1996
  - Gudes, Scott US Senate, TO: Dec. 11, 1995
  - Guenther, Paul B. SIA Securities Industry Association, TO: Apr. 20, 1995
  - Gutierrez, Luis V. US House of Representatives, FROM: Oct. 10, 1996; May 9, 2000; TO: Dec. 10, 1996; Jun. 20, 2000
  - Guttag, Irwin Mentor Partners, L.P. FROM: Jul. 27, 1993; TO: Aug. 4, 1993
  - Gupta, Rajat K. McKinsey & Co., Inc. TO: Jan. 29, 2001
  - Gut, Rainer E. Credit Suisse, Switzerland, FROM: Jun. 25, 1996; TO: Jul. 11, 1996; Dec. 24, 1998
  - Guthary, Barry Securities Division, MA, TO: Apr. 21, 1995
  - Guy, Joel Boy Scouts of America, TO: Mar. 24, 1998
  - Haaga, Paul G., Jr. Capital Research and Management Co. FROM: Oct. 27, 2000; TO: Mar. 16, 1999; Dec. 7, 2000
  - Haberle, Therese M. Charles Schwab & Co, Inc. From: Feb. 6, 1996; TO: Feb. 17, 1995; Mar. 6, 1996
  - Hafer, Fred D. GPU, Inc. TO: Dec. 5, 1997
  - Hafner, Joseph A., Jr. Riviana Foods, Inc. FROM: Jul. 15, 1997; TO: Jul. 23, 1997
  - Hageman, Hans, TO: Oct. 21, 1998
  - Haire, John R. Dean Witter InterCapital, Inc. TO: Mar. 16, 1999
  - Halik, Rebecca St. Ignatius School, FROM: Jan. 8, 1996; TO: Feb. 20, 1996
  - Hall, Hannah R. Los Angeles Times, FROM: Apr. 18, 1995 (See Miller, Allan C.)
  - Hall, J. Andrew Comision Nacional de Valores, Argentina, TO: Jan. 24, 2001
  - Hall, Ralph M. US House of Representatives, FROM: Sep. 26, 1996; Jan. 8, 1997; Jul. 3, 1997; TO: Mar. 27, 1995; Oct. 28, 1996; Feb. 10, 1997; Jul. 24, 1997
  - Hallman, Cinda Dupont Global Systems and Processes, TO: Aug. 20, 1999; May 17, 2000
  - Halloran, Michael J. Bank of America; Pillsbury, Madison & Sutro, FROM: Mar. 21, 1995; TO: Apr. 10, 1995; Aug. 29, 1997
  - Hamill, Tom, TO: Jan. 11, 1995
  - Hammerman, Stephen L. Merrill Lynch & Co, Inc. FROM: Oct. 2, 1995; TO: Jul. 7, 1995; Oct. 5, 1995
  - Hankin, Joseph N. Westchester Community College, NY, TO: Mar. 16, 1999
  - Hanks, Eva H. Yeshiva University, FROM: Sep. 14, 1993 (See also Lamm, Sep. 21, 1993)
  - Hannigan, Barbara B. US SEC - Ethics Liason Officer, FROM: (See Kennedy James) Mar. 27, 1995; Jan. 10, 2001
  - Hannon, Kerry USA Today, FROM: Apr. 9, 1998; TO: Apr. 14, 1998
  - Hansell, William H., Jr. International City/County Management Association, TO: Jan. 9, 1997
  - Hansen, William Education Finance Council, TO: Jan. 9, 1997
  - Hanssen, Kris DLS Group, Inc. TO: Feb. 17, 1995
  - Hantke, Wolfgang Organization for Economic Cooperation and Development, FROM: Nov. 28, 1996 (Aaron, David); TO: Dec. 30, 1996
  - Harbin, Roger F. PNMR Securities, Inc. TO: Apr. 20, 1995
  - Hardiman, Joseph R. National Association of Securities Dealers, Inc. FROM: Mar. 11, 1996; TO: Jan. 12, 1995; Feb. 17 1995; Apr. 26, 1995; Jul. 7, 1995; Mar. 21, 1996
  - Hardy, John US SEC - OIEA, TO: [Aug. 7], 1998; Jul. 17, 2000
  - Harkin, Tom US Senate, FROM: Mar. 25, 1998; TO: Apr. 28, 1998
  - Harmon, Jim Wertheim, Schroder, TO: Apr. 26, 1995
  - Harmon, Sidney, TO: Apr. 27, 1999
  - Harper, Ken, FROM: Jul. 29, 1999; TO: Aug. 17, 1999
  - Harper, Terry US SEC, TO: Sep. 29, 1995
  - Harrington, Diana Babson College, TO: May 14, 1998
  - Harris, Dee Riddell Arizona Corporation Commission; North American Securities Administrators Association, Inc. FROM: Aug. 9, 1993; TO: Aug. 24, 1993; Dec. 5, 1995
  - Harris, Edwina US SEC - Office of Administrative and Personnel Management, TO: Jan. 23, 2001
  - Harris, Hubert L. INVESCO Retirement & Benefit Services, TO: May 14, 1998
  - Harrod, James Edward D. Jones & Co. TO: Feb. 17, 1995
  - Hart, Dabney G. Cosmos Club, TO: Aug. 16, 2000